{
    "subject": "resource/Bob_Hoskins",
    "predicate": "property/deathDate",
    "object": "2014-04-29",
    "human_readable": "Bob Hoskins died on April 29, 2014.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8321599960327148,
            "question": "When did Bob Hoskins die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7586589455604553,
            "question": "What year was Bob Hoskins's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3898254930973053,
            "question": "In what month did Bob Hoskins pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3842078447341919,
            "question": "Was Bob Hoskins a famous actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3198195695877075,
            "question": "What is Bob Hoskins remembered for in the world of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31177178025245667,
            "question": "What was Bob Hoskins best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2533351182937622,
            "question": "Did Bob Hoskins win any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22484077513217926,
            "question": "How would you describe Bob Hoskins's acting style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2219456434249878,
            "question": "What type of roles did Bob Hoskins often play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2142704576253891,
            "question": "Name some of Bob Hoskins's notable films."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bob Hoskins died on April 29, 2014.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4259_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles did Bob Hoskins often play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4259_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Bob Hoskins's acting style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4259_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Bob Hoskins win any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4259_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4259_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple instances confirming that Bob Hoskins passed away on April 29, 2014."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}